Silva Keci

Date of birth: 20/06/2000 | Nationality: Albanian | Gender: Female | Phone number: (+355) 0692122415 (Mobile) |

Email address: silvakeci05@gmail.com | **Website:** https://silva-portfolio.netlify.app/ | **LinkedIn:**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/silva-keci | WhatsApp Messenger: 0692122415

Address: Tirane, Albania, 1001, Tirana, Albania (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for the technology industry. I have excellent mathematical logic skills, enabling me to find the most effective and optimal solution to the problem. I am seeing a part-time / full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2024 - CURRENT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER HAWKFIELDS

As a software developer at Hawkfields, I develop my skills in:

- React.js, React Native (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript)
- Redux.js, Context API, Material-UI, Axios, React Router
- · Jira project management tool
- Problem-Solving and Troubleshooting
- Git version control

01/02/2022 - 31/08/2024 Tirana, Albania

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER GRANIT

As a software developer at GranIT, I develop my skills in:

- React.js, React Native (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript)
- Redux.js, Context API, Material-UI, Axios, React Router
- · Jira project management tool
- Git version control

01/11/2022 - 01/02/2023 Tirana, Albania

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTESA SANPAOLO BANK

As a software developer at Intesa Sanpaolo Bank, I work with:

- Java Programming language with Spring Boot framework.
- MySQL Database
- Git version control
- · Jira project management tool

01/04/2021 - 01/06/2021

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER ELITE ACADEMY (INTERNSHIP)

As a software developer at Elite Academy, I work with:

- C# Programming language with Spring Boot framework.
- MySQL Database
- Git version control
- React Is

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2019 - 14/07/2023 Tirana, Albania

ENGINEERING MATHEMATICAL AND INFORMATICS University of Tirana

- Computer ArchitectureData Structures and AlgorithmsProbability and Statistics

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ALBANIAN**

Other language(s): **ENGLISH**